Contact

+ 371 29120790 (Mobile) info@yvette.lv

www.linkedin.com/in/ivetadmitrijeva (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

PHP

React.js

JavaScript

Languages

French (Limited Working)
Latvian (Native or Bilingual)
Russian (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Iveta Dmitrijeva

Junior Front-end Developer

Luxembourg, Luxembourg, Luxembourg

Summary

Creative thinker with the ability to manage client demands and to turn their visions into a high-quality web-based solutions. Reliable professional with 12 years of experience in banking sector and 3 years of experience in entrepreneurship seeking to start a career in information technology industry.

Experience

Yvette Ltd ENTERPRENEUR

August 2015 - June 2018 (2 years 11 months)

Riga, Latvia

Private business entrepreneurship. General management of the company.

Accounting and control of the financial activities. Marketing development (ex: participation in a TV show and publication in the magazines, social media)

Nordea

SENIOR CREDIT RSIK ANALIST

January 2010 - August 2015 (5 years 8 months)

Riga, Latvia

SME Credit committee member. Analysis and evaluation the overall level of solvency of the corporate client. Presenting recommendations to credit committees. Modifying and restructuring of existing loans. Creating financial projections.

Swedbank Latvija

5 years 9 months

Corporate Client Manager

June 2007 - October 2009 (2 years 5 months)

Riga, Latvia

Developing and maintaining customer relationships. Prepare credit proposal and follow up the whole credit approval process of the Bank. Provide products and services to the clients. Achieve sales and revenue targets as set by management.

Page 1 of 2

Credit Risk Analyst February 2004 - June 2007 (3 years 5 months) Riga, Latvia

Analysis and evaluation the overall level of solvency of the corporate client. Presenting recommendations to credit committees. Modifying and restructuring of existing loans. Creating financial projections

Education

NumericALL

Junior Web Developer / Coding Jobs Professional Training, Web Development · (June 2022 - September 2022)

University of Latvia Faculty of Business, Management and Economics

Bachelor's degree , Business Administration and Management, General · (September 2001 - June 2006)